[Music]
and
control yourself throughout the whole
range of motion
[Music]
where i have a picture of all this stuff
just a good squeeze you're not thinking
[Music]
[Applause]
who is
in 2006 i invented the barbell hip
thrust
i am the creator of innovative strength
training equipment including the hip
thruster
the t-belt and the hammy track and
roller
i conduct numerous experiments in
published research
i create monsters in my gym i'm the
creator of the sport of strong lifting
and i'm the og glute guy who created
this whole niche
i have a phd a cscs certification with
distinction
i have almost 30 years of lifting and 25
years of personal training under my belt
i recently deadlifted 635 pounds
beltless and almost hit 650.
i've spoken at over 70 conferences and
seminars worldwide
published over 50 peer-reviewed journal
articles
authored three books opened up three
glute labs
and assembled one badass group of women
who call themselves the glute squad
and this is just the beginning
[Music]
so rather than just dive into things i
felt it would be appropriate to start
this whole thing off
with an introduction i have accumulated
200 000 youtube subscribers
i used to upload videos left and right
back in the day
you know we do it in one take i had a
broken camera that i dropped
and it gave me a lisp i don't have a
list but in that
original videos i talked like this
i am brett contress so i have never
given youtube my all
the past few years i've really focused
on instagram and i've amassed a million
followers there but i want to see if i
can get a million
youtube followers in one year so really
i need eight hundred thousand more
now in order to do this i'm gonna have
to learn youtube i'm gonna have to treat
you guys
like a family and basically do what i've
done for instagram
so i plan on responding to comments and
kind of getting a feel for youtube and
learning what you guys like and don't
like
so to expedite the process i hired a
video guy named alex to live with me i
give him the upstairs room of my las
vegas house
i'm also gonna fly a bunch of my glute
squad members from san diego over here
every week now a bonus with that is that
we'll get a lot of behind the scenes
footage
but the plan as for now which will
probably change over time is to come out
with
four different videos a week so yeah
we're talking like
200 videos this year now one of those
videos will be
the exercise of the week and that's
where i'll really delve into the
biomechanics
surrounding that lift and really do it
justice another will be a topic of the
week video
you know how often should i trade my
glutes things like that
one will be training in behind the
scenes footage basically i train a ton
of people and i want to highlight
the methods that i use and then also
show off the fun that we have
and also showcase some of the hard work
that goes into my my businesses and my
brand
like what i do for booty babrat and bc
strength
and all the projects that i'm involved
in and then finally just a random video
each week which could be
a new product i'm coming out with or
just something funny or unique
so that's four videos a week and i'm
particularly excited to give you an
inside scoop into my life and all the
traveling back and forth between las
vegas and san diego
and i also plan on taking a lot of trips
this year
to do speaking and strong lifting meets
and also i want you to get to know some
of the characters in my life
some of my business partners and
especially my glute squad
you know many of them are hilarious but
they're all very unique
and i want you to get to know them just
as i have i think you'll really like
some of my people
now i am sacrificing a lot in 2021 like
i'm basically using my house
as like an airbnb that i also live in
i'm gonna have people here around the
clock i'm gonna have no privacy
i don't think any girl you know i'm
single i don't think any woman would
want to date me
when i've got a camera in my face and
like
six women staying with me at all times
not that i'm complaining
2022 will probably be the year that i
finally get a girlfriend
i am gonna work my ass off this year and
hard work is not foreign to me
i do work my ass off but this year is
going to be brutal
one of my goals is to bring my squad up
and try to elevate them and
teach them a lot of the things i've
learned in in the industry
in terms of how to gain more reach and
generate more revenue
but this is a really cool house you know
i will do a cribs episode and you can
check it out
but my squad and i have a lot of fun and
i want you to see that too
because you can work hard and play hard
you know my squad is
a lot of very unique individuals but we
just mesh
very well and we all support each other
so i invite you to subscribe to my
channel
and prepare yourself for a crazy year of
hopefully very educational and very
entertaining
video content